Your mind will not accept a game this big.
Revolver is a drama, thriller, crime film directed by Guy Ritchie.
Hotshot gambler Jake Green is long on bravado and
seriously short of common sense.
Rarely is he allowed in any casino because he's a bona fide winner and, in fact, has taken so much
money over the years that he's the sole client of his accountant elder brother, Billy.
Invited to a private game, Jake is in fear of losing his life.
Jake Green, played by Jason Statham.
Macha, played by Ray Liotta.
Zach, played by Vincent Pastore.
Avi, played by André 3000.
French Paul, played by Terence Maynard.
Billy, played by Andrew Howard.
Revolver is a 2005 action thriller film co-written and directed by Guy Ritchie, and
starring Jason Statham, Ray Liotta, Vincent Pastore, and André Benjamin.
The film centres on a revenge-seeking confidence trickster whose weapon is a universal formula
that guarantees victory to its user, when applied to any game or confidence trick.
This is the fourth feature film by Ritchie and his third to
centre on crime and professional criminals.
It was released in UK cinemas on 22 September 2005.
It performed poorly at the box office and received negative reviews.
A reworked version was released to a limited number
of US theatres on 7 December 2007.
The film explores themes of cash, wrong diagnosis,
foretelling, waterboarding, safe box.
The tone is mind_bending and emotional and intense.